ASIF IBRAHIM

+971 504896797, +91 963 3372980 aasyvt01@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/asif-ibrahim

ARCHITECT

ABOUT ME

A novice architect who is a dedicated learner with an unwavering passion for exploring new design perspectives, driven by the belief that architecture should evoke deep emotional connections while harmonizing with the natural environment. Skilled in CAD, 3D- Modeling, Realistic Rendering and Virtual Reality presentation. I am always excited to embrace new experiences, learn from diverse environments, and collaborate with seasoned professionals to push the boundaries of design.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURE

College of engineering and technology Payyanur, India (2019–2024)

HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION

CHMKS GHSS Mattool, India (2015-2017)

HIGHSCHOOL EDUCATION

CHMKS GHSS Mattool, India (2012-2015)

LANGUAGE

English (intermediate)
Hindi (intermediate)
Malayalam (fluent)
Arabic (beginner)

SKILLS

TECHNICAL PROFESSIONAL

AutoCAD
Photoshop
Revit
SketchUp
Rhino
Lumion
D5 render
Twinmotion
VRav

Adaptability
Communication
Leadership
Organization
Attention to details
Computer literacy
Critical thinking
Team building

MS office

CERTIFICATIONS

COA registered certification

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE | ARCHITECT

2021-2024

VOLNA architects- Kannur, Kerala, India

On going residential projects Kannapuram and Puthiyangadi, Kerala, India

Site visit - For better understanding the laborers in the masonry stage

3D DEVELOPER I PART TIME

2021-2024

NWC builders and developers Payyanur, India

Worked as 3D developer, covering site visits for the interior design contractors.

Worked under the Eng. Waseem Wahab

ARCHITECT | INTERN

SEP 2022 - JAN 2023

Studio Avocado Calicut, India

As part of my academic program, the KTU's 7th semester mandates 100 days of internship with an architect. I completed my internship at Studio Avocado in Calicut under the Yasin KM

VOLUNTEER AND LEADERSHIP

IIA Kerala state awards 2021

IIA young architects' festival, crossroads 2022

Nationals service scheme VOLUNTEER APJ Abdul kalam

University Kerala, India

COORDINATOR - Urban design studio'23 Kannur, India

ACADEMIC HIGHLIGHTS

STUDY TOUR

2019-2023 (Agra, Jaipur, Delhi, Manali)

WORKSHOP

Sketching workshop by Ar. Albin & Ar. Akhil (2021-2022)

EXHIBITION

Ente Kannur exhibition organised by IIA Kannur with college of engineering and technology Payyanur and

college of engineering and technology Thiruvananthapuram, India